import 'package:quiz/pages/Question.dart';

class QuestionsBank {
  List<Question> questions = [
    Question(question: '15*7=115', ans: false),
    Question(question: '3/3=0', ans: false),
    Question(question: '18-4=16', ans: false),
    Question(question: '33+22=55', ans: true),
    Question(question: '100-34=76', ans: false),
    Question(question: '25*5=135', ans: false),
    Question(question: '243+17=260', ans: true),
    Question(question: '50/20=20.5', ans: false),
    Question(question: '18+82=100', ans: true),
    Question(question: '56-40=6', ans: false),
  ];
}
